Contact

rachellesimsrn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rachelle-sims-54a816131 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ELNECELNEC Traing all levels all staff MD ->unit handyman

ELNECELNEC Traing all levels all staff MD ->

ELNEC

Rachelle Sims

WHAT HAVE YOU GOT FOR ME? I am FREE April 26, 2020....to pick up on the next contract or position!

Cloverdale, Indiana

Summary

Currently licensed in Indiana &North Dakota. Experienced in ICU, Step-care, Telemetry, Med/Surg, ER Consulting specialist and educator Palliative Care; ELNEC, train-the-trainer, PC for ICU thru clinic, training staff/nursing & support staff bedside. . float experience coverage/VA...EVERY UNIT AND CLINIC as well. Additional coursework & clinical (Circulator) OR, Pre-op, post-op training thru IUSON @ St Vincent 2003.

\$3 million 3 yr renewable grant with addition of my performance numbers/consults.

Experience

Self-employed
BSN,RN,ELNEC, independant & travel contracting.
September 2014 - Present (5 years 11 months)
Indiana & North Dakota

St. Joseph's Hospital Weekend House Admin Supervisor September 2019 - Present (11 months)

Responsible for staffing, productivity tracing, facilitating facility flow, administrative reports, responding to all code levels/active participant, staffing ABH admissions with intake staff, all bed control, staff issues, active listening, resolutions, deesculating all patient, family, and staff actions.

Notifying appropriate Directors with transfer information or incident. Active/interactive rounding thru each unit, face to face interactions with each coworker at least twice each shift, staffing updates on each unit for any concerning patients or planned discherges. Retrieval of anything that is needed thru out the weekend I.e. Tube feed, box lunches, compassion carts, etc.

Soley responsible for facility during weekend overnights.

Register Nurse, Nurse manager at LTS February 2016 - June 2017 (1 year 5 months)

Greencastle, Indiana

RVAMC

11 years 5 months

RN, BSN, ELNEC

June 2003 - September 2014 (11 years 4 months)

Indianapolis, Indiana

Started in SICU as Valor Student 06/2003assigned to SICU, coverage included entire hospital/Re-signed as permanent RN 06/2004//recruited to Palliative Care as Consultant/liaison, and symptom management specialist 11/2008, see resume for additional duties and ask about duties shared with my amazing Sr RN Carol Jordan. I was offered full benefit/paid retirement & officially retired FEDRI 08/2014.

Registered Nurse

May 2003 - August 2014 (11 years 4 months)

Indianapolis, Indiana

BSN RN ELNEC.

May 2003 - August 2014 (11 years 4 months)

Indianapolis, Indiana

Retired 8/14. Independent contractor since retirement.

RAVMC

Registered Nurse

November 2008 - August 2014 (5 years 10 months)

Indianapolis, Indiana

Education

IUSON, IIUPUI, IVY TECH, ISU

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2003)